Guide to the Public Art Fund Archive 1966-2009 MSS.270
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VI: Public Art Fund - Project Files, 179139
  - Subseries VI.A: Exhibitions and Projects (1977 - 2009), 1972-2009; 179600
    - Sugarman, George - "Purple and Yellow" - 1 of 2, 1985; 181816 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Sugarman, George - "Purple and Yellow" - 2 of 2, 1985; 181817 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Adams, Dennis, 1986-1988; 184678 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Adams, Dennis, 1986-1988; 184679 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Arman - 1 of 4, 1986; 181818 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Arman - 2 of 4, 1986; 181819 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Arman - 3 of 4, 1986; 181820 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Arman - 4 of 4, 1986; 181821 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Bourgeois, Louise, 1986; 181822 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Dennis, Donna, 1986; 181823 (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - Elrod, Biff - 1 of 2, 1986; 181824 (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - Elrod, Biff - 2 of 2, 1986; 181825 (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - Ferrara, Jackie, 1986; 181826 (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - Finn, David, 1986; 184680 (Box 40, Folder 26)
    - Finn, David - "Wild Mouse" - Coney Island, Brooklyn New York, 1986; 192008 (Box 40, Folder 27)
    - Giordano, Joe, 1986; 181827 (Box 40, Folder 28)
    - Greenblat, Rodney Alan, 1986; 181828 (Box 40, Folder 29)
    - Hammons, David - "Higher Goals" - 1 of 2, 1986; 181829 (Box 40, Folder 30)
    - Hammons, David - "Higher Goals" - 2 of 2, 1986; 181830 (Box 40, Folder 31)
    - Klavun, Betty, 1986; 181831 (Box 40, Folder 32)
    - Miyazaki, Stomu, 1986; 181832 (Box 40, Folder 33)
    - Morellet, Francois - 1 of 2, 1986; 181833 (Box 40, Folder 34)
    - Morellet, Francois - 2 of 2, 1986; 181834 (Box 40, Folder 35)
    - Rickey, George, 1986; 181835 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Rupp, Christy, 1986; 181836 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Artschwager, Richard, 1987; 181837 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Aycock, Alice, 1987; 184981 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Culkin, Jody, 1987; 181838 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Finkelpearl, Tom, 1987; 181839 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Jones, Kristin and Andrew Ginzel, 1987; 181840 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Knowlton, Grace, 1987; 181841 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - LeWitt, Sol, 1987; 181842 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Messner, Ann, 1987; 181843 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Saunders, David, 1987; 181844 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Wegman, William, 1987; 181845 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Birch, Willie, 1988; 181846 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Casebere, James, 1988; 181847 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Heap-of-Birds, Edgar, 1988; 181848 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Hewat, Christopher, 1988; 181849 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Group Material - "Inserts" - 1 of 2, 1988; 181858 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Group Material - "Inserts" - 2 of 2, 1988; 181859 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Kramer, Margia, 1988; 181850 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Kruger, Barbara, 1988; 181851 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Lawson, Thomas, 1988; 181852 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1988; 181853 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Min, Yong Soon, 1988; 181854 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Nonas, Richard, 1988; 181855 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Schafer, David, 1988; 181856 (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - Wilson, Fred, 1988; 181857 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Dwyer, Nancy, 1989; 181860 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Gaskin, Franco - "Franco the Great", 1989; 181861 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - General Idea - 1 of 3, 1989; 181862 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - General Idea - 2 of 3, 1989; 181863 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - General Idea - 3 of 3, 1989; 181864 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Gianakos, Steve, 1989; 181865 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Gonzalez-Torres, Felix - 1 of 2, 1989; 181867 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Gonzalez-Torres, Felix - 2 of 2, 1989; 181866 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Greengold, Jane, 1989; 181868 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Holzer, Jenny, 1989; 181869 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Katz, Joel - 1 of 3, 1989; 181871 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Katz, Joel - 2 of 3, 1989; 181870 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Katz, Joel - 3 of 3, 1989; 181872 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Kearns, Jerry, 1989; 181873 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Ladda, Justen, 1989; 181874 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Lemieux, Annette, 1989; 181875 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Rivera, Sophie, 1989; 181876 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Rollins, Tim + K.O.S. - 1 of 2, 1989; 181877 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Rollins, Tim + K.O.S. - 2 of 2, 1989; 181878 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - Subway posters - General, 1989; 184982 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Van Dalen, Anton - 1 of 2, 1989; 181879 (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - Van Dalen, Anton - 2 of 2, 1989; 181880 (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - Winokur, Neil, 1989; 181881 (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - Bursztyn, Dina, 1989; 181882 (Box 42, Folder 25)
    - Cowin, Eileen, 1989; 181883 (Box 42, Folder 26)
    - Fulbrecht, William - "Seeds", 1990; 185035 (Box 42, Folder 27)
    - Fulbrecht, William - "Bill of Rights", 1990; 182073 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Goulet, Michel, 1990; 182074 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Horsfield, Kate & Klonarides, "Carol Anne - Video Drive-in"/Central Park, 1990; 182075 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Menard, Andrew, 1990; 182076 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Meredith, Ann, 1990; 182077 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Michelson, Alan, 1990; 185036 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Muntadas, Antonio - 1 of 2, 1990; 182078 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Muntadas, Antonio - 2 of 2, 1990; 182079 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Nordman, Maria, 1990; 182080 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Shapiro, Joel, 1990; 182081 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Wong, Martin, 1990; 182082 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Cole, Jeffrey and Schafer, David, 1991; 182083 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Dill, Terry Lee, 1991; 182084 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Edwards, Melvin, 1991; 182085 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Gran Fury, 1991; 182086 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Guerrilla Girls, 1991; 182087 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Kroke, Pit, 1991; 182088 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - Kruger, Barbara, 1991; 182089 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1991; 182090 (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - Ressler, Robert, 1991; 182091 (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - Aiha, Martti, 1992; 182092 (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - Allen, Jules, 1992; 182093 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Deon, Richard - 1 of 2, 1992; 182094 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Deon, Richard - 2 of 2, 1992; 182095 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Hauft, Amy - 1 of 2, 1992; 182096 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Hauft, Amy - 2 of 2, 1992; 182097 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Lee, Bing and Garson Yu, 1992; 182098 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Moore, Jesse, 1992; 182099 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Sonfist, Alan, 1992; 182100 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - "Trans Voices" - General - 1 of 2, 1992; 182101 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - "Trans Voices" - General - 2 of 2, 1992; 182102 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - "Trans Voices" - Declined, 1992; 182103 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - "Trans Voices" - Blain, Dominique, 1992; 182104 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - "Trans Voices" - Boltanski, Christian, 1992; 182105 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - "Trans Voices" - Cazal, Philippe, 1992; 182106 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - "Trans Voices" - Ennadre, Touhami, 1992; 182107 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - "Trans Voices" - Gerz, Jochen, 1992; 182108 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - "Trans Voices" - Jaar, Alfredo, 1992; 182109 (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - "Trans Voices" - Lafontaine, Marie-jo, 1992; 182110 (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - "Trans Voices" - Messager, Annette, 1992; 182111 (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - "Trans Voices" - Simmons, Laurie, 1992; 182112 (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - "Trans Voices" - Simpson, Lorna, 1992; 182113 (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - "Trans Voices" - Teraoka, Masami, 1992; 182114 (Box 44, Folder 22)
    - "Trans Voices: Questions for a New Order", 1992; 198458 (Box 44, Folder 23)
    - Botero, Fernando - 1 of 3, 1993; 182115 (Box 44, Folder 24)
    - Botero, Fernando - 2 of 3, 1993; 182116 (Box 44, Folder 25)
    - Botero, Fernando - 3 of 3, 1993; 182117 (Box 44, Folder 26)
    - Bunkley, Brit, 1993; 182118 (Box 44, Folder 27)
    - di Suvero, Mark, 1993; 184309 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Lacy, Suzanne - 1 of 2, 1993; 184310 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Lacy, Suzanne - 2 of 2, 1993; 184311 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Pepper, Beverly - 1 of 2, 1993; 184313 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Pepper, Beverly - 2 of 2, 1993; 184314 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Shearer, Rhonda Ronald - 1 of 2, 1993; 184317 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Shearer, Rhonda Ronald - 2 of 2, 1993; 184318 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - "Urban Paradise" - 1 of 5, 1993; 184319 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - "Urban Paradise" - 2 of 5, 1993; 184320 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - "Urban Paradise" - 3 of 5, 1993; 184321 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - "Urban Paradise" - 4 of 5, 1993; 184322 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - "Urban Paradise" - 5 of 5, 1993; 184323 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Boyer, Gilbert, 1994; 184324 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Flanagan, Barry, 1994; 184325 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Jones, Kristin and Andrew Ginzel, 1994; 184326 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Jordan, Lorna, 1994; 184327 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Ladda, Justen, 1994; 184328 (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Mitchell, Tyrone, 1994; 184329 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Saar, Alison and Betye, 1994; 184330 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Shea, Judith, 1994; 184386 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Simmons, Gary, 1994; 184387 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Steinbach, Haim, 1994; 184388 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Strang, Gary; Roche, Michael; and Hewitt, Robert - "Urban Paradise", 1994; 184389 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Webster, Meg, 1994; 184391 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Acconci, Vito (1 of 2), 1995; 184392 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Acconci, Vito (2 of 2), 1995; 184393 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Boltanski, Christian - "Lost" (1 of 5), 1995; 184394 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Boltanski, Christian - "Lost" (2 of 5), 1995; 184395 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Boltanski, Christian - "Lost" (3 of 5), 1995; 184396 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Boltanski, Christian - "Lost" (4 of 5), 1995; 184397 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Boltanski, Christian - "Lost" (5 of 5), 1995; 184398 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - "What They Remember" Interviews, [1995]; 201062 (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Abakanowicz, Magdalena - "Hand-Like Trees", 1996; 184401 (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Brodsky, Alexander (1 of 2) - "Canal Street Subway Project", 1996; 184402 (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - Brodsky, Alexander (2 of 2) - "Canal Street Subway Project", 1996; 184403 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Doyle, Chris - "Commutable", 1996; 185196 (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - Green, Gregory - "Gregnik Proto II", 1997; 185197 (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - Keith Haring on Park Avenue, 1 of 4, 1997; 185198 (Box 46, Folder 20)
    - Keith Haring on Park Avenue, 2 of 4, 1997; 185199 (Box 46, Folder 21)
    - Keith Haring on Park Avenue, 3 of 4, 1997; 185200 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Keith Haring on Park Avenue, 4 of 4, 1997; 185201 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Kabakov, Ilya - "Monument to the Lost Glove", 1 of 2, 1997; 185202 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Kabakov, Ilya - "Monument to the Lost Glove", 2 of 2, 1997; 185203 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Kabakov, Ilya - "Permit", 1997; 192278 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Kruger, Barbara - "Bus", 1997; 185204 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Lipski, Donald - "The Yearling", 1997; 185205 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Saar, Alison and Betye - "Roots and Wings Garden", 1997; 185206 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - De Kooning, Willem, 1998; 185207 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Mosher, Kirstin - "Ball Park Traffic", 1998; 185208 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Rodin, Auguste at Rockefeller Center, 1 of 2, 1998; 185209 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Rodin, Auguste at Rockefeller Center, 2 of 2, 1998; 185210 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Smith, Tony - 1 of 3, 1998; 185211 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Smith, Tony - 2 of 3, 1998; 185212 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Smith, Tony - 3 of 3, 1998; 185213 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Whiteread, Rachel - "Water Tower" - 1 of 3, 1998; 185214 (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Whiteread, Rachel - "Water Tower" - 2 of 3, 1998; 185215 (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Whiteread, Rachel - "Water Tower" - 3 of 3, 1998; 185216 (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - Whiteread, Rachel - Multiple, 1998; 192279 (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - Witz, Dan - "Sticks", 1998; 185217 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Acconci, Vito - "Rooms from Below: A Display System for Show Windows", 1999; 185218 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Baron, Ron - "Birds", 1999; 185219 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Gonzalez, Maria Elena - "Magic Carpet/Home", 1999; 185220 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Grennan, Simon and Christopher Sperandio - "The Invisible City", 1999; 185221 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Hill, Christine, 1999; 185222 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Jones, Kristin and Andrew Ginzel - "Metronome", 1 of 6, 1999; 185223 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Jones, Kristin and Andrew Ginzel - "Metronome", 2 of 6, 1999; 185224 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Jones, Kristin and Andrew Ginzel - "Metronome", 3 of 6, 1999; 185225 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Jones, Kristin and Andrew Ginzel - "Metronome", 4 of 6, 1999; 185226 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Jones, Kristin and Andrew Ginzel - "Metronome", 5 of 6, 1999; 185227 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Jones, Kristin and Andrew Ginzel - "Metronome", 6 of 6, 1999; 185228 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Manship, Paul Howard - "Manship at Rockefeller Center", 1999; 185237 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Matelli, Tony - "Distant Party", 1999; 185238 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Zittel, Andrea - 1 of 4, 1999; 185239 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Zittel, Andrea - 2 of 4, 1999; 185240 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Zittel, Andrea - 3 of 4, 1999; 185241 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Zittel, Andrea - 4 of 4, 1999; 192275 (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - Beecroft, Vanessa - 1 of 2, 2000; 185242 (Box 48, Folder 19)
    - Beecroft, Vanessa - 2 of 2, 2000; 185362 (Box 48, Folder 20)
    - Creed, Martin, 2000; 185468 (Box 48, Folder 21)
    - Kabakov, Ilya & Emilia - "Palace of Projects" - 1 of 5, 2000; 185469 (Box 48, Folder 22)
    - Kabakov, Ilya & Emilia - "Palace of Projects" - 2 of 5, 2000; 185470 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Kabakov, Ilya & Emilia - "Palace of Projects" - 3 of 5, 2000; 185471 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Kabakov, Ilya & Emilia - "Palace of Projects" - 4 of 5, 2000; 190519 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Kabakov, Ilya & Emilia - "Palace of Projects" - 5 of 5, 2000; 190520 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Koons, Jeff - "Puppy" - 1 of 2, 2000; 185472 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Koons, Jeff - "Puppy" - 2 of 2, 2000; 185473 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Kruger, Barbara, 2000; 185474 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Long, Richard - 1 of 2, 2000; 185475 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Long, Richard - 2 of 2, 2000; 185476 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Oursler, Tony - 1 of 2, 2000; 185477 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Oursler, Tony - 2 of 2, 2000; 185478 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Rist, Pipilotti - "Open My Glade", 2000; 185479 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Taylor, Jocelyn - "The Story of Color", 2000; 185480 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Von Rydingsvard, Ursula - Bowl with Folds, 2000; 185481 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Weiner, Lawrence - "New York City Manhole Covers", 2000; 185482 (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Westphalen, Olav - "E.S.U.S. Extremely Site Un-Specific Sculpture", 2000; 185483 (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - Bourgeois, Louise - 1 of 2, 2000; 185484 (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - Bourgeois, Louise - 2 of 2, 2001; 185485 (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - Cragg, Tony - "Turbo and Ferryman", 2001; 185486 (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - Fernández, Teresita - "Bamboo Cinema", 2001; 185487 (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - McCarthy, Paul - "The Box", 2001; 185488 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - McElheny, Josiah - "The Metal Party: Reconstructing a Party held in Dessau on February 9, 1929" - 1 of 2, 2001; 185489 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - McElheny, Josiah - "The Metal Party: Reconstructing a Party held in Dessau on February 9, 1929" - 2 of 2, 2001; 190521 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Pfeiffer, Paul - "Orpheus Descending", 2001; 185490 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Ramirez Jonas, Paul - "Every Day", 2001; 185491 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Rawanchaikul, Navin - "I Love Taxi" - 1 of 3, 2001; 185492 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Rawanchaikul, Navin - "I Love Taxi" - 2 of 3, 2001; 185493 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Rawanchaikul, Navin - "I Love Taxi" - 3 of 3, 2001; 185494 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Rehberger, Tobias - 1 of 3, 2001; 185495 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Rehberger, Tobias - 2 of 3, 2001; 185496 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Rehberger, Tobias - 3 of 3, 2001; 185497 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Alÿs, Francis - "The Modern Procession" - 1 of 2, 2002; 185498 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Alÿs, Francis - "The Modern Procession" - 2 of 2, 2002; 190522 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Dalziel + Scullion - "Voyager", 2002; 185499 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Dion, Mark - "Urban Wildlife Observation", 2002; 185500 (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Edmier, Keith - "Emil Dobbelstein and Henry J. Drope, 1944", 2002; 185501 (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Freeman, Jonah - Sixteen Scenarios, 2002; 185502 (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Freeman, Jonah & Mack, Anissa, 2002; 190523 (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - Graham, Dan - Bisected Triangle, Interior Curve, 2002; 185503 (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - Mack, Anissa - Pies for a Passerby, 2002; 185504 (Box 50, Folder 20)
    - Muniz, Vik - CandyBAM, 2002; 185505 (Box 50, Folder 21)
    - Munoz, Juan - "Conversation Piece" - 1 of 2, 2002; 185506 (Box 50, Folder 22)
    - Munoz, Juan - "Conversation Piece" - 2 of 2, 2002; 190524 (Box 50, Folder 23)
    - Paik, Nam June - "Transmission", 2002; 187325 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Paik, Nam June - "Transmission" - Press/ Anne Wehr, 2002; 189855 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Paine, Roxy - "Bluff", 2002; 188071 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Smith, Kiki - "Sirens and Harpies", 2002; 188072 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Sooja, Kim - "Deductive Object", 2002; 188073 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Tolle, Brian - "Waylay", 2002; 188074 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Delvoye, Wim - "Gothic Works", 2003; 189873 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Delvoye, Wim - "Caterpillar" & "Chantier", 2003; 188075 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Handforth, Mark - "Lamppost", 2003; 188076 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Mori, Mariko - "Wave UFO" - Press, 2003; 188077 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Mori, Mariko - "Wave UFO" - Contracts, 2003; 188078 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Mori, Mariko - "Wave UFO" - Project plan, 2003; 188079 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Mori, Mariko - "Wave UFO" - Installation, 2003; 188080 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Mori, Mariko - "Wave UFO" - Budget, 2003; 188081 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Mori, Mariko - "Wave UFO" - Intern questionnaire, 2003; 188082 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Mori, Mariko - "Wave UFO" - Press - Anne Wehr 1 of 2, 2003; 189880 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Mori, Mariko - "Wave UFO" - Press - Anne Wehr 2 of 2, 2003; 189881 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Murakami, Takashi - "Reversed Double Helix" - 1 of 6, 2003; 188083 (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Murakami, Takashi - "Reversed Double Helix" - 2 of 6, 2003; 188084 (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - Murakami, Takashi - "Reversed Double Helix" - 3 of 6, 2003; 188085 (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - Murakami, Takashi - "Reversed Double Helix" - 4 of 6, 2003; 188086 (Box 51, Folder 21)
    - Murakami, Takashi - "Reversed Double Helix" - 5 of 6, 2003; 188087 (Box 51, Folder 22)
    - Murakami, Takashi - "Reversed Double Helix" - 6 of 6, 2003; 189882 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Segal, George - "Street Crossing", 2003; 188088 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Williams, Clara - "The Price (Giving in Gets You Nowhere)", 2003; 188089 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Altmejd, David - "Untitled (Swallow)" and "Untitled (Bluejay)", 2004; 188091 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - assume vivid astro focus, 2004; 188092 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Borofsky, Jonathan - 1 of 3, 2004; 188093 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Borofsky, Jonathan - 2 of 3, 2004; 188094 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Borofsky, Jonathan - 3 of 3, 2004; 189987 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Cardiff, Janet - "Her Long Black Hair" - 1 of 6, 2004; 188095 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Cardiff, Janet - "Her Long Black Hair" - 2 of 6, 2004; 188096 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Cardiff, Janet - "Her Long Black Hair" - 3 of 6, 2004; 188097 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Cardiff, Janet - "Her Long Black Hair" - 4 of 6, 2004; 188098 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Cardiff, Janet - "Her Long Black Hair" - 5 of 6, 2004; 188099 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Cardiff, Janet - "Her Long Black Hair" - 6 of 7, 2004; 188100 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Cardiff, Janet - "Her Long Black Hair" - 7 of 7, 2004; 190135 (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Craft, Liz - "The Spare", 2004; 190147 (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Haring, Keith, 2004; 190148 (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - Kereszi, Lisa & Moore, Andrew - "Governor's Island" - 1 of 2, 2004; 190149 (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - Kereszi, Lisa & Moore, Andrew - "Governor's Island" - 2 of 2, 2004; 190150 (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - Kusama, Yayoi - "Narcissus Garden", 2004; 190151 (Box 52, Folder 20)
    - McCarthy, Paul - "Daddies Bighead", 2004; 190152 (Box 52, Folder 21)
    - McCollum, Allan - "Perfect Vehicles", 2004; 190153 (Box 52, Folder 22)
    - Muller, Dave - "Themeless (A Carnival of Sorts)", 2004; 190154 (Box 52, Folder 23)
    - Opie, Julian - "Animals, Buildings, Cars, and People" - 1 of 5, 2004; 190155 (Box 52, Folder 24)
    - Opie, Julian - "Animals, Buildings, Cars, and People" - 2 of 5, 2004; 190156 (Box 52, Folder 25)
    - Opie, Julian - "Animals, Buildings, Cars, and People" - 3 of 5, 2004; 190157 (Box 52, Folder 26)
    - Opie, Julian - "Animals, Buildings, Cars, and People" - 4 of 5, 2004; 190158 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Opie, Julian - "Animals, Buildings, Cars, and People" - 5 of 5, 2004; 190235 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - West, Franz - 1 of 3, 2004; 190236 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - West, Franz - 2 of 3, 2004; 190237 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - West, Franz - 3 of 3, 2004; 190238 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Westphalen, Olav - "The Weight of Dead Prey", 2004; 190239 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Deacon, Richard - "Masters of the Universe": Screen Version, 2005; 190240 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Deacon, Richard - "Masters of the Universe": Screen Version - 2 of 2, 2005; 190241 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Diaz, Alejandro - "A Can For All Seasons", 2005; 190242 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Huyghe, Pierre - "A Journey That Wasn't" - 1 of 5, 2005; 190243 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Huyghe, Pierre - "A Journey That Wasn't" - 2 of 5, 2005; 190244 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Huyghe, Pierre - "A Journey That Wasn't" - 3 of 5, 2005; 190245 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Huyghe, Pierre - "A Journey That Wasn't" - 4 of 5, 2005; 190246 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Huyghe, Pierre - "A Journey That Wasn't" - 5 of 5, 2005; 190247 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Kentridge, William - "9 Drawings for Projection" - 1 of 3, 2005; 190301 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Kentridge, William - "9 Drawings for Projection" - 2 of 3, 2005; 190302 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - Kentridge, William - "9 Drawings for Projection" - 3 of 3, 2005; 190303 (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - Murakami, Takashi - "Cool Japan", 2005; 190304 (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - Murakami, Takashi - "Little Boy" - 1 of 9, 2005; 190305 (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - Murakami, Takashi - "Little Boy" - 2 of 9, 2005; 190306 (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - Murakami, Takashi - "Little Boy" - 3 of 9, 2005; 190307 (Box 53, Folder 21)
    - Murakami, Takashi - "Little Boy" - 4 of 9, 2005; 190308 (Box 53, Folder 22)
    - Murakami, Takashi - "Little Boy" - 5 of 9, 2005; 190309 (Box 53, Folder 23)
    - Murakami, Takashi - "Little Boy" - 6 of 9, 2005; 190310 (Box 53, Folder 24)
    - Murakami, Takashi - "Little Boy" - 7 of 9, 2005; 190311 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Murakami, Takashi - "Little Boy" - 8 of 9, 2005; 190312 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Murakami, Takashi - "Little Boy" - 9 of 9, 2005; 190313 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Smith, Allison - "The Muster" - 1 of 4, 2005; 190314 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Smith, Allison - "The Muster" - 2 of 4, 2005; 190315 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Smith, Allison - "The Muster" - 3 of 4, 2005; 190316 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Smith, Allison - "The Muster" - 4 of 4, 2005; 190317 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Smith, Allison - "The Muster" - Images - 1 of 2, 2005; 201063 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Smith, Allison - "The Muster" - Images - 2 of 2, 2005; 201064 (Box 54, Folder 9)